sportsmanswarehouse.co.za 2018-10-30

# Privacy Policy | Sportsmans Warehouse

#### MORESPORT (PTY) LTD TRADING AS SPORTMANS WAREHOUSE

  1. ##### Moresport's Privacy Policy

Moresport respects consumers' constitutional rights to privacy and data protection. Accordingly, Moresport believes in protecting the personal information we collect from you when you use the www.sportmanswarehouse.co.za website ("our website"). Moresport will use its best commercial endeavours to only use or disclose your personal information in the manner stated in this policy.

This privacy policy forms part of the Moresport website terms and conditions.

  2. ##### Personal information

Personal information refers to all information about you as an identifiable individual, including your name, address, e mail address, telephone number, and identity number.

  3. ##### Personal information collected

    1. Limited personal information is collected using cookies. A cookie is an alphanumeric identifier which we transfer to your hard drive through your web browser when you visit our website. It enables our own system to recognise you when you visit our website again and to improve our service to you. Cookies may also be used to compile aggregate information about areas of our website that are visited most frequently. This information can be used to enhance the content of our website and make your use of it easier. We do not monitor which pages you looked at while visiting our website. You can disable our use of cookies by configuring your browser accordingly.
    2. In order to register for certain services or to enter competitions or promotions offered through our website Moresport will from time to time ask you for relevant personal information. Moresport will use such information to provide the services to you. Moresport may also use such information for its own internal purposes including– 
      1. establishing and verifying your identity;
      2. maintaining and updating our customer databases; and
      3. marketing, product research and development purposes.
  4. ##### Storage of personal information

    1. Moresport uses all reasonable endeavours to put in place and maintain electronic procedures and systems to ensure accuracy and to prevent unauthorised access to your personal information with reference to accepted technological standards.
    2. Virtual Card Services process all credit card transactions. All credit card transactions are 128 bit Secure Socket Layers (SSL) encrypted.

VCS's registration documents and the site's registered domain name are checked and verified by Thawte, ensuring the cardholder and merchant that nobody can impersonate VCS to obtain confidential information. Virtual Card Services is committed to providing secure online services. All encryption complies with international standards. Encryption is used to protect the transmission of personal information when completing online transactions. Virtual Card Services Internet servers are protected by firewalls and intrusion detection systems. The Merchant does not have access to credit details. Virtual Card Services continually reviews and enhances its security in line with technological changes.

  5. ##### Personal information shared

    1. Moresport will not sell, rent or otherwise disclose your personal information to any third party without your consent, provided that by using our website and/or subscribing for any of our services, you provide your express and informed consent for Moresport to disclose your personal information to third parties as follows:

      1. to third party companies employed by Moresport to provide services for us, including for example, website hosting and development. These companies require access to your personal information to perform their functions and not for any other purposes;
      2. to transfer Moresport's customer database/s, including personal information contained therein, to any third party who acquires all or substantially all of the assets or shares in our company or our website service whether by sale, merger, acquisition or otherwise;
      3. to governmental agencies, exchanges and other regulatory or self-regulatory organisations if Moresport is required to do so by law or if we believe that such action is necessary to:

        1. comply with the law or with any legal process;
        2. protect and defend our rights and property or that of our customers and companies in our group;
        3. prevent fraud or abuse, misuse or unauthorised use of our website; and/or
        4. protect the personal safety or property of our customers or the public (if you provide false or deceptive information about yourself or misrepresent yourself as being someone else, Moresport will disclose such information to the appropriate regulatory bodies and commercial entities).

    2. Moresport reserves the right to share non-personal, non-individual information in aggregate form with third parties for business purposes, for example with advertisers on our website or business associates and partners. This does not involve disclosing any personal information which can identify any individual consumer in any way.

  6. ##### Legal Disclaimer

    1. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information to governmental bodies, exchanges and other regulatory or self-regulatory organisations if Moresport is required to do so by law or if we believe that such action is necessary as set out in 5.1.3.
    2. In addition, we may disclose information if required to do so to any regulatory authorities in connection with any investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose Moresport to legal liability.
  7. ##### Links

Our website contains links to other websites. Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of third party websites or the manner in which they use cookies and advise you to read the privacy statements of each website you visit which collects personal information.

  8. ##### Communicating with us

It is very important that the information that Moresport has about you is accurate and current. If you would like to receive a copy of the information we hold about you (subject to our right to charge you a fee to cover our expenses in this regard), to correct or update your information, or to ask any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us.

  9. ##### Communicating with you / Opting Out

We provide you the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication.

  10. ##### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we decide to change our privacy & security policy, we will post changes to this page. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

The amended privacy & security policy will supersede and replace any previous policies with effect from the date on which it is posted on our website.

  11. ##### Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy & security policy, please email the Webstore at [onlinesales@sportsmanswarehouse.co.za](mailto:onlinesales@sportsmanswarehouse.co.za).

* * *
